

■ lkellyandroid@gmail.com □ 647-936-9245

# Professional Summary

I am a 20 year old Web Developer who is excited to enter the work force. I love everything that has to do with Web design & development and specialize in front end work. I am experienced in all stages of the development cycle for web applications and am constantly learning through my personal and freelance projects. Feel free to contact me by email or phone if you're interested in working with me, I'd love to chat.

## Experience

## **Developer Intern**

Critical Mass, Toronto, ON, May 2017 - August 2017

Worked on a team of six to design a new mobile banking experience for Citi Bank. Lead a company project to create a predictive AI for Nissan Canada

### **WEB DEVELOPER INTERN**

F1V Web Design & Development, Watertown, MA, May 2015 - September 2016

Worked as a web developer intern during the summers of 2015 and 2016. My responsibilities included maintaining current websites by responding to tickets as well as creating new web applications to meet the needs of clients.

## **CABLECASTER AND WEB MAINTAINER**

Bolton Access TV, Bolton, MA, December 2010 - September 2015

- ·Assisted in the broadcasting of cable television in the town of Bolton
- ·Worked to configure various equipment (cameras, microphones, soundboards, software packages).
- ·Troubleshooted server problems to ensure the network ran smoothly
- ·Redesigned the company website to be sleeker and more user-friendly

# Projects

## **Explore TO**

Co-founded and worked as the front end developer in a small team to create a new venue and event-based platform to help millennials find new and interesting things to do in Toronto.

www.explore6.herokuapp.com

#### Nissan Al

Created an AI for Nissan Canada to predict the lead conversion rate for a user as they visit the site. The AI assigned a probability and cluster to that user, and then used several factors to determine which steps should be taken to help them on their consumer journey.

#### **UofT Course Rater and Course Distances**

Created a web application using a MEAN stack for reviewing courses at the University of Toronto as well as seeing the time and distances between classes.

## **Linden Photonics**

Redesigned the website for Linden Photonics to create a more modern, responsive, and user-friendly site that the company could maintain in the future using Wordpress.

## www.liamckelly.com

Personal website written using HTML, CSS and Javascript/JQuery.

## Education

#### Diploma

St. John's High School • Shrewsbury, MA • 2015 • 3.7 GPA

## **Attended**

University of Toronto • Toronto, ON • 2015-2017

# Skills

Java • HTML + CSS • Javascript & Jquery • Angular JS • React JS • Node JS & Express • Git & SVN • Wordpress • Android Development • Machine Learning